Register of the Friedrich A. von Hayek papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Incremental Materials I, 1922-2003
  - Speeches and Writings II, 1922-1993
    - Letter to the editor, Presse, typescript, 1963 June 14 (Box-folder 108: 7)
    - "The Legal and Political Philosophy of David Hume," lecture, Universität Freiburg, Freiburg, Germany, 1963 July 18 (Box-folder 108: 8)
      Published in Hume: A Collection of Critical Essays, 1966. Printed copy
    - "A Table of Contrasts Supplied in Amplification of the Lecture on General Welfare and Particular Purpose," London, England, typescript, 1965 January 18 (Box-folder 108: 9)
    - "Annual Report of the Walter Eucken Institute for the Year 1966," typescript (Box-folder 108: 10)
    - "Personal Recollections of Keynes and the ‘Keynesian Revolution'," printed copy, Oriental Economist, 1966 January (Box-folder 108: 11)
    - "The Misconception of Human Rights as Positive Claims," printed copy, Farmand, 1966 December (Box-folder 108: 12)
    - "Commerce, History of," Encyclopedia Brittanica, printed copy, 1967 (Box-folder 108: 13)
    - "The Meanings of ‘Law and Order'," lecture, Stanford University, Stanford, California, typescript, 1968(?) (Box-folder 108: 14)
    - "Marktwirtschaft oder Syndikalismus," Protokoll des Wirtschaftstages der CDU/CSU 1969, printed copy (Box-folder 108: 15)
    - "Zwolf Thesen zum Inflationsproblem," typescript, 1970s (Box-folder 108: 16)
    - "Can We Still Avoid Inflation?" lecture, New York, typescript, 1970 (Box-folder 108: 17)
    - "Enterprise Can Still Free Itself," typescript, 1970 (Box-folder 108: 18)
    - "Die Irrtumer des Konstruktivismus und die Grundlagen legitimer Kritik gesellschaftlicher Gebilde," 1970 - Spanish translation, Estudios publicos, printed copy, 1988 Spring (Box-folder 108: 19)
    - Law, Legislation and Liberty: A New Statement of the Liberal Principles of Justice and Political Economy, volume 1, 1973
      - French translation, typescript (Box-folder 108: 20)
      - German translation
        - Holograph and typescript (Box-folder 108: 21)
        - Review, printed copy (Box-folder 108: 22)
    - "The Pretence of Knowledge," Nobel Memorial Lecture, Stockholm, Sweden, 1974 December 11 (Box-folder 108: 23)
      Published in Assar Lindbeck (ed.), Economic Sciences 1969-1980, 1992. Printed copy
    - "Types of Mind," Encounter, printed copy, 1975 (Box-folder 108: 24)
    - "Vollbeschäftigung um Jeden Preis?" speech, Freiburg, Germany, two holographs in German and one holograph in English, 1975 January 28 (Box-folder 108: 25)
    - "Economics, Politics and Freedom," interview, Reason, printed copy, 1975 February (Box-folder 108: 26)
    - "Inflation, the Misdirection of Labour, and Unemployment," speech, Convegno internazionale Il problema della moneta oggi, Rome, Italy, 1975 February 6-8 (Box-folder 108: 27)
      Published in Atti del convegni lincei 12, 1976. Printed copy
    - "Totalitäre Gesitzgebung," speech, Salzburg, Austria, holograph, 1975 February 25 (Box-folder 108: 28)
    - "Geldpolitik und Beschäftigung," speech, Salzburg, Austria, holograph, 1975 March 5 (Box-folder 108: 29)
    - "The Formation of the Open Society," commencement address, University of Dallas, Irving, Texas, typescript, 1975 May 18 (Box-folder 108: 30)
    - Interview conducted by Leonard Silk(?), typescript, 1975 June 29 (Box-folder 108: 31)
    - "Politicians Can't Be Trusted with Money," speech, Gold and Monetary Conference, Lausanne, Switzerland, 1975 September (Box-folder 109: 1)
      Published in Research Reports, American Institute for Economic Research, 1976 February 23. Printed copy
    - "Inflation und Beschaftigung," speech, Vereinigung Österreichischer Industrieller, Salzburg, Austria, printed announcement and typescript, 1975 October 2 (Box-folder 109: 2)
    - "Die neue Konfusion über ‘Planwirtschaft'," printed copy, Industrie, 1976 March 5 (Box-folder 109: 3)
    - "Institutions May Fail, But Democracy Survives," interview, U.S. News & World Report, typescript and printed copy, 1976 March 8 (Box-folder 109: 4)
    - "The F. A. Hayek Issue," IPA Review, 1976 October-December (Box-folder 109: 5)
      Contains two articles by Hayek, "Address at the 33rd Annual Meeting of the Institute of Public Affairs" and "Socialism and Science." Typescript and printed copy
    - Television interview, "Monday Conference" program, Australian Broadcasting Commission, letter and printed copy, 1976 October 11 (Box-folder 109: 6)
    - "The Inseparability of Economic and Political Freedom," lecture, Foundation for Economic Education, Brisbane, Australia, typescript, 1976 October 13 (Box-folder 109: 7)
    - "Wohin zielt die Demokratie?" speech, Individuelle Freiheit und kollektive Wohlfahrt, Sozialwissenschäftliches Forschungsinstitut der Konrad-Adenauer-Stiftung, Bonn-Bad Godesberg, Germany, typescript, 1976 December 9-11 (Box-folder 109: 8)
    - "Ich fürchte um den Markt," interview, Thema, printed copy, 1977 (Box-folder 109: 9)
    - "Die Illusion der sozialen Gerechtigkeit," typescript, 1977 (Box-folder 109: 10)
    - "Den Markt besser begreifen," interview, Wirtschaftswoche, printed copy, 1977 February 11 (Box-folder 109: 11)
    - "Das totalitäre Gesicht des Sozialismus," Frankfürter Allgemeine Zeitung, printed copy, 1977 June 11 (Box-folder 109: 12)
    - Letter to the editor, Times (London), incomplete typescript, 1977 July 14 (Box-folder 109: 13)
    - "An Interview with Friedrich Hayek," Libertarian Review, printed copy, 1977 September (Box-folder 109: 14)
    - "Coping with Ignorance," Ludwig von Mises Lecture, Hillsdale College, Hillsdale, Michigan, 1977 November 8 (Box-folder 109: 15)
      Published in Imprimis 1978 July. Typescript and printed copy.
    - "Towards a Free-Market Monetary System," paper, 4th Annual New Orleans Financial and Economic Conference, New Orleans, Louisiana, 1977 November 10 (Box-folder 109: 16)
      Published in Journal of Libertarian Studies, 3, no. 1, 1979. Typescript and printed copy.
    - "La inflacion es la mayor amenaza contra la libertad," interview, Somos, printed copy, 1977 November 25 (Box-folder 109: 17)
    - "Internationaler Rufmord: Eine personliche Stellungnahme," Studien, printed copy, 1977 November 30 (Box-folder 109: 18)
    - New Studies in Philosophy, Politics, Economics and the History of Ideas, 1978
      - Preface, typescript, 1976 July (Box-folder 109: 19)
      - Spanish translation of chapter 7, published in Estudios Publicos, printed copy, 1986 Winter (Box-folder 109: 20)
    - Remarks, Frankfürt International Monetary Conference, Frankfürt, Germany, related correspondence and transcript, 1978 (Box-folder 109: 21)
    - Temas de la hora actual, 1978 (Box-folder 109: 22)
      Spanish translation of speeches delivered at La Academia Nacional de Ciencias Economicas, Buenos Aires, Argentina. Printed copy.
    - "La discipline de la liberte," speech, Gesellschaft für soziale Marktwissenschaft(?), Bonn-Bad Godesberg, Germany, - French translation, typescript, 1978 January 23 (Box-folder 109: 23)
    - Letters to the editor, Times (London), four typescripts, 1978 June 5 - July 27 (Box-folder 109: 24)
    - Foreward to Murray Rothbard, Individualism and the Philosophy of the Social Sciences, typescript, 1979 (Box-folder 109: 25)
    - "Inside the Hayek Equation," film, printed transcript, 1979 (Box-folder 109: 26)
    - "Liberalismo," Enciclopedia del novecento, proofs and printed copy, 1979 (Box-folder 109: 27)
    - Letter to the editor, Economist, typescript, 1979 January 3 (Box-folder 109: 28)
    - Speech accepting the Ludwig-Erhard-Preis für Wirtschaftspublizitik, Bonn, Germany, annotated program and typescript, 1979 February 2 (Box-folder 109: 29)
    - Acceptance speech, typescript, 1979 May 10 (Box-folder 109: 30)
    - "Planificacion: Nueva confusion," Caretas, printed copy, 1979 September 17 (Box-folder 109: 31)
    - Letters to the editor, Presse, two typescripts and enclosure, 1979 October 10-29 (Box-folder 109: 32)
    - "A Period of Muddle-Heads," interview, Newsweek, printed copy, 1979 November 5 (Box-folder 109: 33)
    - Foreward to Pascal Salin, European Monetary Unity, For Whose Benefit?, typescript, 1980 (Box-folder 109: 34)
    - "Die wirtschaftlichen Gefahren zum Beginn der 80er Jahre," radio address, Westdeutscher Rundfunk, typescript and printed copy, 1980 January 2 (Box-folder 109: 35)
    - "De dwaalsporen van het konstruktivisme," printed copy, Trends, 1980 January 15 (Box-folder 109: 36)
    - Letter to the editor, Times (London), typescript, 1980 January 28 (Box-folder 109: 37)
    - "Sozialismus zerstört die personliche Freiheit," interview, printed copy, Welt, 1980 January 28 (Box-folder 109: 38)
    - Letter to the editor, Times (London), typescript, 1980 February 26 (Box-folder 109: 39)
    - Letter to the editor, Economist, typescript, 1980 March 18 (Box-folder 109: 40)
    - Interview, American Economic Council Report, printed copy, 1980 May (Box-folder 109: 41)
    - Letter to the editor, Times (London), typescript, 1980 June 7 (Box-folder 109: 42)
    - "Sozialismus - eine Illusion," symposium remarks, Industriemagazin, printed copy, 1980 August (Box-folder 109: 43)
    - "The Increasing Gap," typescript, 1980 September 15 (Box-folder 109: 44)
    - "Friedrich Hayek ou la route de la liberte," interview, Express, 1980 December 13 (Box-folder 109: 45)
      Printed copies of original and Portuguese translation published in Cultura, 1981 February.
    - "Ungleichheit is nötig," interview, proofs and printed copy, Wirtschaftswoche, 1981 March 6 (Box-folder 109: 46)
    - Letter to the editor, Times (London), typescript, 1981 March 12 (Box-folder 110: 1)
    - "Un largo itinerario de libertad," interview, printed copy, Ercilla, 1981 April 29 (Box-folder 110: 2)
    - Speech, 31st meeting of Nobel laureates, Lindau, Germany, typescript, 1981 June 28 (Box-folder 110: 3)
    - Letter to the editor, Times (London), typescript, 1981 July 17 (Box-folder 110: 4)
    - "The Changing Range and Content of Individual Responsibility," speech, 5th International Humanistic Symposium, Portaria, Greece, holograph and typescript, 1981 September (Box-folder 110: 5)
    - "The Flaws in the Brandt Report," Times (London), printed copy, 1981 September 1 (Box-folder 110: 6)
    - "Der Sozialismus - die fatale Einbildung," interview, Finanz und Wirtschaft, printed copy, 1981 September 9 (Box-folder 110: 7)
    - "Zwei Seelen wohnen, Ach! in meiner Brust," speech, Tokyo, Japan, holograph fragment and typescript, in English, 1981 November 4 (Box-folder 110: 8)
    - Letter to the editor, Times (London), holograph, 1981 November 14 (Box-folder 110: 9)
    - "Inflation and Unemployment," holograph fragment and typescript, 1982 (Box-folder 110: 10)
    - Speech on cultural development, Schloss Klessheim Pfingstsymposium, Salzburg, Austria, typescript, 1982 (Box-folder 110: 11)
    - "Britain's Economic Miracle: Is It Still Within Grasp?," interview, Director, printed copy, 1982 February (Box-folder 110: 12)
    - "Individualism and the Extended Society," address, The Economics Society, University College, Dublin, Ireland, holograph notes and program, 1982 March 16 (Box-folder 110: 13)
    - "Two Pages of Fiction: The Impossibility of Socialist Calculation," Economic Affairs, printed copy, 1982 April (Box-folder 110: 14)
    - Letter to the editor, Times (London), typescript, 1982 June 22 (Box-folder 110: 15)
    - "Our Moral Heritage," lecture sponsored by the Heritage Foundation, Washington, D.C., 1982 November 29 (Box-folder 110: 16)
      Typescript of original and printed copy of Spanish translation published in Diario de Caracas, 1985 March 24.
    - Interview, Silver & Gold Report, printed copy, 1982 December (Box-folder 110: 17)
    - "Samtale med Hayek," interview, Ideer om Frihet, printed copy, 1983 January (Box-folder 110: 18)
    - Letter to the editor, Times (London), typescript, 1983 January 11 (Box-folder 110: 19)
    - "Lohnpolitik der Gewerkschaften ist zu starr," interview, Welt, printed copy, 1983 February 4 (Box-folder 110: 20)
    - Letter to the editor, Times (London), typescript, 1983 February 10 (Box-folder 110: 21)
    - "Friedrich Hayek on the Crisis," interview, Encounter, printed copy, 1983 May (Box-folder 110: 22)
    - "Einzelwissen und Gesamtordnung," speech in honor of Adolf Butenandt, Freiburg, Germany, typescript and printed copy, 1983 May 14 (Box-folder 110: 23)
    - "Una sera, al King's College sconfesso i suoi allievi," Sole-24 hora, printed copy, 1983 June 4 (Box-folder 110: 24)
    - "The Keynes Centenary: The Austrian Critique," Economist, correspondence, typescript, and printed copy, 1983 June 6 (Box-folder 110: 25)
    - "Evolution and Spontaneous Orders," speech, Lindau, Germany, holograph and incomplete typescript, 1983 June 28 (Box-folder 110: 26)
    - "Aims of Industry," speech in acceptance of International Free Enterprise Award, London(?), England, incomplete holograph, 1983 July 4 (Box-folder 110: 27)
    - "Sitte, Ordnung und Nährung," Frankfürter Allgemeine Zeitung, printed copy, 1983 July 30 (Box-folder 110: 28)
    - "Wir zahlen für unsere Dummheiten," interview, Wochenpresse, printed copy, 1983 August 16 (Box-folder 110: 29)
    - "The Weasel Word ‘Social'," Salisbury Review, printed copy, 1983 Autumn (Box-folder 110: 30)
    - "The Rules of Morality Are Not the Conclusions of Our Reason," speech, 12th International Conference on the Unity of the Sciences, Chicago, Illinois, 1983 November 25
      - Typescript, printed copy, and clipping (Box-folder 110: 31)
      - German translation published in Conturen, and Neue Zürcher Zeitung, printed copies, 1984 May 15 (Box-folder 110: 32)
    - "Nei - Keynes var ikke keynesianer," Farmand, printed copy, 1983 December (Box-folder 110: 33)
    - "The Future Unit of Value" in Pascal Salin (ed.), Currency Competition and Monetary Union, 1984 (Box-folder 110: 34)
      Incorporates elements of lectures given at the Institutum Europaeum, 1980 December 2, and at the Visa International Annual Conference, Athens, Greece, 1981 September 14. Printed copy.
    - Der Strom der Guter und Leistungen, 1984 (Box-folder 110: 35)
      Printed copies of original and excerpt published in Wirtschaftswoche, 1984 March 30.
    - "Un inédit de F. A. Hayek," Tribune des nouveaux politiques, printed copy, 1984 February (Box-folder 110: 36)
    - "Hayek: ‘Pourquoi le socialisme ne peut marcher'," interview, Actualite, printed copy, 1984 February 18 (Box-folder 110: 37)
    - Speech, Mont Pèlerin Society conference, Paris, France, 1984 March 3 (Box-folder 110: 38)
      Typescript of original and printed copy of French translation published in Figaro Magazine, 1984 March 10.
    - "Von Hayek, gourou du liberalisme ultra," interview, Le Monde, 1984 March 11-12 (Box-folder 110: 39)
      Printed copies of original and Italian translation published in Chi e liberale, chi e socialista, 1984.
    - Letter to the editor, Times Literary Supplement, typescript, 1984 April 4 (Box-folder 110: 40)
    - "The Rules of Morality Are Not the Conclusions of Our Reason," speech, Turin, Italy, 1984 April 14 (Box-folder 110: 41)
      Notes and typescript (text differs from speech of the same title delivered in Chicago, Illinois, 1983 November 25).
    - Interview, Cato Policy Report, printed copy, 1984 May-June (Box-folder 110: 42)
    - "Die ‘Bevölkerungsexplosion'," radio broadcast, Deutschlandfunk, typescript transcript including Hayek's remarks, 1984 May 16 (Box-folder 110: 43)
    - "Die Regeln der Moral sind nicht Schlussfolgerungen unserer Vernünft," speech and discussion, Freiburg, Germany, 1984 May 24 (Box-folder 110: 44)
      Typescript transcript (text differs substantially from speeches in English of the same title).
    - "Preissignale im Produktionsprozess," Bilanz, printed copy, 1984 June (Box-folder 110: 45)
    - "Jobs: The Basic Truths We Have Cast Aside," Times (London), printed copy, 1984 August 7 (Box-folder 111: 1)
    - "Entmachtung der Macht durch den Markt," interview, Finanz und Wirtschaft, printed copy, 1984 October 1984 (Box-folder 111: 2)
    - "Socialismo y ciencia," Diario de Caracas, printed copy, 1984 November 11 (Box-folder 111: 3)
    - "Die ausgedehnte Ordnung menschlicher Zusammenarbeit," speech, Peutinger-Collegium, Munich, Germany, 1984 November 15 (Box-folder 111: 4)
      Published in Bayerischer Monatsspiegel, 1984 December. Printed copy.
    - Interview conducted for Investment Rarities, Inc., correspondence and typescript, 1985 (Box-folder 111: 5)
    - "Gerechtigkeit gibt es nicht," interview, Profil, printed copy, 1985 April 1 (Box-folder 111: 6)
    - Letter to the editor, Times (London), holograph and typescript, 1985 April 21 (Box-folder 111: 7)
    - "Eine intellektuelle Wende im Westen," interview, printed copy, Welt, 1985 May 2 (Box-folder 111: 8)
    - "Die Überheblichkeit der Vernünft," speech, Hanns Martin Schleyer-Stiftung, Stuttgart, Germany, two typscripts, 1985 May 3 (Box-folder 111: 9)
    - "Keine Angst vor Bevölkerungsexplosion," interview, Welt, printed copy, 1985 May 8 (Box-folder 111: 10)
    - "Entretien avec Friedrich Von Hayek," interview, Contrepoint, 50-51, printed copy, 1985 Autumn (Box-folder 111: 11)
    - "Market Standards for Money," Economic Affairs, printed copy, 1986 April-May (Box-folder 111: 12)
    - Speech accepting the International Cultural Foundation Founder's Award, 1986 April 14 (Box-folder 111: 13)
      Published in ICUS Report, 1987 January. Printed copy.
    - The Fatal Conceit: The Errors of Socialism, 1988
      - Unincorporated material, typescript and holograph (Box-folder 111: 14)
      - Notes and fragments (Box-folder 111: 15)
      - Typescripts consisting of two separate, incomplete drafts, with holograph corrections (Box-folder 111: 16-22)
      - Publicity material (Box-folder 111: 23)
      - Reviews and comments, typescripts and printed copies, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 111: 24)
      - Spanish translation of introduction, printed copy, 1988 (Box-folder 112: 1)
      - Malay translation, printed copy, 1993> (Box-folder 112: 2)
    - "Population Bomb Is Being Defused by Affluence," Wall Street Journal, printed copy, editorial commentary, and correspondence, 1988 December 6 (Box-folder 112: 3)
    - "Macht und Übermacht," Innovatio, printed copy, 1989 (Box-folder 112: 4)
  - Academic Career File II, 1931-1982
    Bibliography, lectures, notes, and outline, arranged chronologically by university.
    - General
      - "Economic Aspects of Certain Social Institutions," lectures 6 and 7, holographs, undated (Box-folder 112: 5)
      - Notes for lectures on money, undated (Box-folder 112: 6)
    - University of London, England - Lectures on monetary theory, notes, 1931
      - Lecture 1 (Box-folder 112: 7)
      - Lecture 3 (Box-folder 112: 8)
      - Lecture 4 (Box-folder 112: 9)
      - Lecture 5 (Box-folder 112: 10)
    - London School of Economics
      - Economic Analysis I, lectures, notes, 1942 (Box-folder 112: 11)
      - Economic Analysis II, lectures, notes, 1943 (Box-folder 112: 12)
      - Economic Analysis III, lectures, notes, 1943 (Box-folder 112: 13)
    - Universität Wien, Vienna, Austria
      - "Geldtheorie," lecture, typescript, 1948 July 15 (Box-folder 112: 14)
      - Lecture (in German) on the Austrian economy, holograph and typescript, 1949 (Box-folder 112: 15)
    - University of Chicago, Committee on Social Thought - Seminar on Equality and Justice, 1950-1951
      - Typescript outline and bibliography (Box-folder 112: 16)
      - Lecture notes (Box-folder 112: 17)
    - Claremont Men's College, Institute on Freedom and Competitive Enterprise, Claremont, California, typescript summaries of lectures, 1956 June (Box-folder 112: 18)
    - Albert-Ludwigs-Universität, Freiburg, Germany - Lecture series, Moral, Wissenschaft und Sozialismus, typscript transcript, 1982 April-June (Box-folder 112: 19)
  - Subject File II, 1937-1988
    Correspondence, memoranda, notes, printed matter, and reports, arranged alphabetically by subject.
    - Cantillon, Richard (Box-folder 113: 1)
      Includes correspondence with Henriette Taylor.
    - City planning--Great Britain (Box-folder 113: 2)
    - Education--Austria (Box-folder 113: 3)
      Includes memoranda prepared by Hayek concerning the Universität Wien and a proposed Institute of Advanced Studies in Vienna.
    - Frankl, Victor E. (Box-folder 113: 4)
    - Gibraltar (Box-folder 113: 5-6)
      Consists of reports made to the Colonial Secretariat in 1944 by Hayek regarding economic conditions in the colony. Includes background material and correspondence.
    - Hutton, Graham (Box-folder 113: 7)
    - Jewkes, John (Box-folder 113: 8)
    - Kaldor, Nicholas (Box-folder 113: 9)
    - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 113: 10)
    - North American Review (Box-folder 113: 11)
    - Poland--History--, 1980-1989 (Box-folder 113: 12)
  - Writings by Others II, 1936-1986
    Articles, books, and speeches, arranged alphabetically by author. Includes many commentaries on Hayek's work.
    - Anastaplo, George (Box-folder 113: 13)
    - Atkinson, Rodney (Box-folder 113: 14)
    - Barger, Melvin D. (Box-folder 113: 15)
    - Berg, Charles A. (Box-folder 113: 16)
    - Bornsen, Ole (Box-folder 113: 17)
    - Brachthauser, Norbert (Box-folder 113: 18)
    - Briskman, Larry (Box-folder 113: 19)
    - Caldwell, Bruce J. (Box-folder 113: 20)
    - Clark, Colin G. (Box-folder 114: 1)
    - Falkena, H. B. (Box-folder 114: 2)
    - Friedman, Milton (Box-folder 114: 3)
    - Galeotti, Anna Elisabetta (Box-folder 114: 4)
    - Gray, John (Box-folder 114: 5)
    - Haberler, Gottfried (Box-folder 114: 6)
    - Heimbach, Stephan (Box-folder 114: 7)
    - Hennings, K. H. (Box-folder 114: 8)
    - Heringer, H. J. (Box-folder 114: 9)
    - Kirzner, Israel M. (Box-folder 114: 10)
    - Kiss, Sylvia (Box-folder 114: 11)
    - Kleinewefers, Henner (Box-folder 114: 12)
    - Lepage, Henri (Box-folder 114: 13)
    - Leung, Physer (Box-folder 114: 14)
    - Lindner, Eberhard (Box-folder 114: 15)
    - Machlup, Fritz (Box-folder 114: 16)
    - Mayr, Paulus (Box-folder 114: 17)
    - Meijer, Gerrit (Box-folder 115: 1)
    - Molsberger, Josef (Box-folder 115: 2)
    - Nadeau, Robert (Box-folder 115: 3)
    - Nemo, Philippe (Box-folder 115: 4-6)
    - Nishiyama, Chiaki. (Box-folder 115: 7)
    - O'Driscoll, Gerald P., Jr. (Box-folder 115: 8)
    - Pahler, Klaus (Box-folder 115: 9)
    - Paqué, Karl-Heinz (Box-folder 115: 10-11)
    - Parish, William J. (Box-folder 115: 12)
    - Radnitzky, Gerard (Box-folder 115: 13-14)
    - Riboud, J. (Box-folder 115: 15)
    - Robbins, L. C. (Box-folder 115: 16)
    - Robertson, D.H. (Box-folder 115: 17)
    - Rowland, Barbara Mehl (Box-folder 115: 18)
    - Salin, Pascal (Box-folder 116: 1)
    - Sanchez Sanudo, Carlos A. (Box-folder 116: 2)
    - Scheide, Joachim (Box-folder 116: 3)
    - Schmidtchen, Dieter (Box-folder 116: 4)
    - Schmieding, Holger (Box-folder 116: 5)
    - Schutz, Alfred (Box-folder 116: 6)
    - Shearmur, Jeremy (Box-folder 116: 7)
    - Shenfield, Arthur (Box-folder 116: 8)
    - Smith, Leif (Box-folder 116: 9)
    - Stigler, George (Box-folder 116: 10)
    - Streissler, Erich (Box-folder 116: 11)
    - Swan, Arthur W. (Box-folder 116: 12)
    - Thalenthorst, Jobst (and Alois Wenig) (Box-folder 116: 13)
    - Traurig, Wolfgang (Box-folder 116: 14)
    - Vanberg, Viktor (Box-folder 116: 15)
    - Wilhelm, Morris M. (incomplete) (Box-folder 116: 16)
    - Woolman, Stuart Craig (Box-folder 116: 17)
    - Wyzanski, Charles (Box-folder 116: 18)
    - Zeitler, Christoph (Box-folder 116: 19)
  - Photographs II, 1931-1934